<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>West Branch Angler &amp; Resort&apos;s Blog</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.westbranchresort.com/apps/blog/data/wba/" />
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.westbranchresort.com/apps/blog/data/wba/atom.xml" />
    <id>tag:www.westbranchresort.com,2008-09-23:/apps/blog/data/wba//2</id>
    <updated>2008-09-23T23:23:12Z</updated>
    <subtitle>The source for upcoming events, new products, river conditions and much much more. </subtitle>
    <generator uri="http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/">Movable Type 4.21-en</generator>

<entry>
    <title>Help Us Stop FFMP</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.westbranchresort.com/apps/blog/data/wba/2008/09/help-us-stop-ffmp.html" />
    <id>tag:www.westbranchresort.com,2008:/apps/blog/data/wba//2.3</id>

    <published>2008-09-23T23:12:16Z</published>
    <updated>2008-09-23T23:23:12Z</updated>

    <summary>&quot;The Delaware River Basin Commission (DRBC) is scheduled to hold a vote on September 24th to amend the Water Code under which the commission operates in order to legitimize the interim Flexible Flow Management Program (FFMP) for the Upper Delaware...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Sam Batschelet</name>
        
    </author>
    
    <category term="westbranchangler" label="West Branch Angler" scheme="http://www.sixapart.com/ns/types#tag" />
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="http://www.westbranchresort.com/apps/blog/data/wba/">
        <![CDATA["The Delaware River Basin Commission (DRBC) is scheduled to hold a vote
on September 24th to amend the Water Code under which the commission
operates in order to legitimize the interim Flexible Flow Management
Program (FFMP) for the Upper Delaware River. Trout Unlimited urges you
to visit our online action center today and tell the DRBC to postpone
the vote on the Water Code until they have fully evaluated the
performance of the interim FFMP and incorporated into the FFMP the
changes required to ensure an ecologically healthy river system." -TU<br /><br /><a href="http://www.tu.org/c.kkLRJ7MSKtH/b.4513901/siteapps/advocacy/ActionItem.aspx">Clik Here To Email Your Opinion</a><br /> <div><br />I am going to the meeting tommarow if anyone wants to go call the shop tomorrow AM/<br /></div>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>New Blog</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.westbranchresort.com/apps/blog/data/wba/2008/09/new-blog.html" />
    <id>tag:www.westbranchresort.com,2008:/apps/blog/data/wba//2.2</id>

    <published>2008-09-23T22:35:16Z</published>
    <updated>2008-09-23T22:43:59Z</updated>

    <summary>The Fall is a slow time for us in general as far as the resort goes but the extra time allows me to work on the site and after thinking long and hard how I was going to improve communications...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Sam Batschelet</name>
        
    </author>
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="http://www.westbranchresort.com/apps/blog/data/wba/">
        <![CDATA[The Fall is a slow time for us in general as far as the resort goes but the extra time allows me to work on the site and after thinking long and hard how I was going to improve communications with everyone I figured a blog would be the best.&nbsp; The forum will still remain active for the next couple of months but then I am going to migrate everyone over to the blog so that I don't have to maintain both.<br /><br />&nbsp;I do want to apologize for the lack of river updates this year&nbsp; Ben and I tried to&nbsp; to stay on top of it but it always seems like we are a behind.&nbsp; The blog is going to help that by making it easier for us to post information.&nbsp; Overall is should be&nbsp; an exciting Fall we have some big plans for the site and lots of new features.&nbsp; Been working with John Miller on&nbsp; getting some more of his wonderful&nbsp; aquatic photography up on the site and&nbsp; working on allowing everyone to use these for fly tying and informational purposes.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Well here it is the first post I am looking forward to testing the features of this program it is very powerful!<br /><br />Tight Loops<br />-Sam<br /> ]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

</feed>
